submitinme.com 2014-06-20

# SIM SEO Services privacy policy

Your privacy is of prime importance to us. This privacy policy is a reflection on how we strive to protect your brand confidentiality. Through this notice we want you to learn that our online SEO project execution process gives you the ultimate power to choose the way your information is collected and used for our SEO services. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available at every page on Submitinme website, where personally identifiable information may be requested.

##  Information collected:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the [company name] website. On some pages, you can register, order services and make custom requests. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Additional info appropriate to projects being managed or serviced by Submitinme.

##  Information Usage Format:

We use the information you provide about your business or your client business when placing an order only to complete that order. We use information provided that is descriptive of a web site as project data unique to that web site. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive and to provide reasonable notification of our project, SEO service or any related information. No such email addresses are shared with outside parties.

Our SEO service sales pages would not advertise your business information as our clients unless until we have the permission for it. We may state statistical information of clients, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those clients, unless you approve of it.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

##  Step Towards Data Security:

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

##  Payment process:

All payments for SEO services is undertaken on Paypal and there is no exchange of sensitive account related information. For Indian residents, bank transfer is accepted and we ensure complete confidentiality of the account information exchanged. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

##  Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy on our SEO services, please call us at 0091 - 4652 - 230776 or send an email to our support team.
